export default [
  
    {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950089",
    "correctAnswer": "Catcher",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pitcher",
      "Guard",
      "Steer"
    ],
    "question": "What Is The Name Of The Player In Baseball Who Is Positioned Behind The Home Plate",
    "tags": [
      "baseball",
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },






  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "6242cb11d543524f1b19c909",
    "correctAnswer": "A murder",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A fall",
      "A cast",
      "A barren"
    ],
    "question": "What is the word for a group of crows?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95010e",
    "correctAnswer": "Sherwood forest",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nottingham",
      "Bedgebury Forest",
      "Hoodwood"
    ],
    "question": "Where did Robin Hood supposedly live?",
    "tags": [
      "uk",
      "fictitious_characters",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fdfa",
    "correctAnswer": "The Rhine ",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Danube",
      "The Seine",
      "The Elbe"
    ],
    "question": "Which River Forms A Border Between France & Germany?",
    "tags": [
      "europe",
      "rivers",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "6260305b4b176d54800e3d1f",
    "correctAnswer": "Santo Domingo",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "San Juan",
      "Valpara√≠so",
      "Cartagena"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these cities is in Dominican Republic?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "6260303f4b176d54800e3d17",
    "correctAnswer": "Dubrovnik",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lisbon",
      "Geneva",
      "Amsterdam"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these cities is in Croatia?",
    "tags": [
      "cities",
      "europe",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "6233854962eaad73716a8c5f",
    "correctAnswer": "Capri",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sicily",
      "Corsica",
      "Crete"
    ],
    "question": "What small island is in the bay of Naples?",
    "tags": [
      "italy",
      "islands",
      "places",
      "bodies_of_water",
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3e7cc59eab6f9522e0",
    "correctAnswer": "Lightning",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Waves",
      "Galaxies",
      "Clouds"
    ],
    "question": "Forked, Sheet, and Ball are types of what?",
    "tags": [
      "science",
      "meteorology"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950589",
    "correctAnswer": "the effects of climate on living organisms",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "friction and lubrication",
      "especially as related to Christianity",
      "wine and winemaking"
    ],
    "question": "What is Bioclimatology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951008",
    "correctAnswer": "A code-breaking computer",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A nuclear-resistant tank",
      "A supersonic bomber",
      "An intercontinental missile"
    ],
    "question": "What Was The Colossus, Developed In Buckinghamshire In 1943?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  }
]